Guide to the David Epel Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Writing/Research, Series 7
  - Collaborative work: AA transport, sea urchin (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Collaborative work: respiration (Paul) (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Collaborative work: Mazia (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Collaborative work: Ziomek (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Collaborative work: Miles, Paul - H+/NH(3) (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Collaborative work: NH(3) paper (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Collaborative work: Fahey (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Jeff Davidson (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Mike Hartke (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Amino acids in SW - uptake (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Current ideas, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Carl's data - Ziomek (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Dave Epel's samples (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Man 8 - sea urchin eggs (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - PHC Mishuka and Epel (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Protein synthesis in sea urchin eggs (Box 10, Folder 59-60)
  - Fertilization inhibition (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Cornwall et. al. paper (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Galgani et. al. paper (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Kuo -- NO paper (Box 10, Folder 64-65)
  - Stricker (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Matia/Steinh. Experiments (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Cornwall paper (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Paul manuscript (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - "Matters Arising" (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - NADK paper (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Scientific American (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Dead manuscripts (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
  - Yasumasu paper (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Collins-Byrd polyspermy (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Localized A23187 on eggs (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - A23187 -- comparative (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Cortical granule -- lack of breakdown (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Cell surface proteins (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Carroll work (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - LaRochelle, Dennis (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Notes (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Dube manuscript (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Dufresne-Dube paper (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Byrd and Collins manuscript (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Plant mitosis (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Unfinished manuscript -- mitotic energetic (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Graph paper (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - SO(4)ase affinity data (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Experiment notes (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Unlabeled notes, possibily related to Bruner paper (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Bruner paper I (Box 11, Folder 25-26)
  - Bruner paper? (Box 11, Folder 27-28)
  - Bruner paper (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Bruner -- SO(4)ase (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Bruner experiments (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Sea urchin facility (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Sea urchin fishery (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Sea urchin problem -- fishery (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Sea urchin -- California Fisheries Institute (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Sea urchin exploitation (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Sea urchin harvesting (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Sea urchin problem (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - ASZ meeting and sea urchin presentation (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Energy alternatives (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Deep sea disposal (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - DDT (Box 11, Folder 42-43)
  - Interdepartmental Liaison Group on Risk Assessment (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - PCB correspondence (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Air pollution / San Diego (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Public pol. letters (Box 11, Folder 47-48)
  - Location of marine organisms (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - SIPI and local issues (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Law/regulation (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Events, Series 8
  - ACS press conference (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Workshop on the ocean's role in human health, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Woods Institute media workshop, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Professional Seminar Consultants, Central Asia (Russia) tour, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Echinoderm conference, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Nagoya meeting, NSF report (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - NATO meeting, Sorrento, Italy, 1989 Oct 1-5 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Marquette symposium, 1990 Mar 16-17 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Developmental Biology of Marine Organisms conference, Plymouth (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Sea urchin meeting, correspondence, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - NATO, 1984 Apr (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Conference/symposium booklets (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Monroy Memorial Symposium (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Hiramoto symposium (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - ASCB mini-symposium, 1989 Jan 29-Feb 2 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - International Marine Center (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - FASEB (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Russian Trip (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - AAAS, 1988 Feb 12-14 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Misaki Lab centennial (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Misaki centennial (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Gordon Conference, 1983 Aug 1-5 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Notes from meeting (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - LJ conference pre-meeting (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Bogeda Bay seminar, 1992 Oct 22 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - ASCB meeting, 1992 Nov 15-19 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - NIH meeting, 1992 May (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Gordon Research Conference, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Participants -- recent meetings (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Commonwealth Club, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Commonwealth Club (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Commonwealth Club talk (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Clean Air Council / La Jolla (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Lectures (text) (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Cornell rotary, etc., 1969 Aug (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Outside lectures -- environment (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Outside lectures -- pesticide pollution (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Friends' lecture (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Lectures -- alumni (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Recent lectures -- alumni/public (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Gordon Conference, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - U.S. / Japan (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Courses, Series 9
  - Zoology 123, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Spring course 1966 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Course summary, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Develop. and Reprod. Biology, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Experiments and reports, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Summer course lectures, 1967, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - 147H, Comparative and Experimental Embryology, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - 175H, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Schedules, 1968-1978 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - 175, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Introductory lecture, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Bio 230, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - La Jolla embryology course, tests and handouts, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - MBL embryology course, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 44-45)
  - Lab, oogenesis and others, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Summer course, workshop on early embryonic development, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Summer course, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Bio 126H, 1979 fall (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Summer 1980 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - 127H, Cell Biology of Early Development, 1981 summer (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Summer course, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 52-53)
  - Spring 1982 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Summer course 1982 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Spring course 1983 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Summer course 1983 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Bio 44X, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Biology 301, 1983-1986 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Biology 44, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Summer course, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Biology 147, circa 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Summer session 1985 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Summer 1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Summer 1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Bio 32, summer 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Bio 147, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Spring course, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Summer, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Course evaluations, signal transduc., 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Spring course, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Summer course, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Summer 1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Summer 1990 (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
  - Summer course, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Spring course, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
  - Summer course, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 16-17)
  - Summer course, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 18-19)
  - Summer course, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Lectures, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Chance, Development, and Aging, schedule and handouts (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Summer courses, miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous summer handouts (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - ONR -- summer course (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Current lectures (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Defense lectures (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Lecture 1 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - First lecture -- articles (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Lecture 2: how to study cells (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - How to write a paper (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Lecture notes (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Summary lecture (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - DNA repair (Box 13, Folder 34-35)
  - Cloning/stem cells (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Cell reproduction (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - MDR/toxins (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Lindquist paper, week 4 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Apoptosis (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Membrane repair (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Aging, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Cancer (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Prions, etc. (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Signal transduction (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Transport (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Plasma membrane (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Cell cycle (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - Motility (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Actin (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Stress (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Course announcements (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Annelida (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
  - Ascidians, lab (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Student work, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Projects, special, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Projects, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Projects, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Fert. projects, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Student work, summer 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 15-16)
  - Student work, summer 1979 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Student work, summer 1982 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Student work, summer 1982 (Box 14, Folder 19-21)
  - Student work, summer 1984 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Student work, summer 1985 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Student work, summer 1986 (Box 14, Folder 24-25)
  - Student work, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Speract and Mobility by Sansoni, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Summer, 1990-1996 (Box 14, Folder 28-29)
  - Student work, spring 1991 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Minisymposia, summer 1991 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Reports, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Student work, 1994-2002 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Cell biology, toxicology papers, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Special projects (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Restricted Files, Series 10
  - Cell physiology, graded student work, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Cell physiology, graded student papers, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
  - Student exams, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Cell physiology, student exams, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Graded Oxford papers, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Library fundraising (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Director search (Box 16, Folder 2-4)
  - Crocker Foundation (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Roughgarden, Jonathan (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Thompson, S. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Gilly reappointment (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Pitt history (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Denny reappointment (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Packard chair (Box 16, Folder 11-13)
  - Somero (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Packard family (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Special donors (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Burnett, Robin and Nancy (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Miller, Mrs. H. (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Thompson (Box 16, Folder 19)